sanyo.com 2015-02-18

# Privacy | Panasonic Global

Head on this page.

* * *

Main Contents begins from here.

This privacy policy is only applicable to the website under [http://panasonic.net](http://panasonic.net/) posted by Panasonic Corporation and its subsidiaries (referred to collectively below as "the Company").

## 1\. Privacy Policy on the Website

The Company aims to obtain the satisfaction and trust of our customers by providing superior products and services, in accordance with our Basic Business Philosophy. As part of our efforts to achieve this goal, we have implemented the following policy to protect your personal information collected on the Company's website.

  1. A person responsible for the protection of personal information has been appointed to every organization within the Company in an effort to ensure that such information is managed appropriately.
  2. In cases where you are asked to supply or register your personal information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number, the Company will inform you of the purpose of use, as well as whom to contact with any related inquiries. You will only be asked to provide your personal information within the scope appropriate to the purpose.
  3. The Company will make use of personal information only within the scope appropriate to the purpose of use to which you have agreed.
  4. The Company will not supply or disclose your personal information to third parties except in cases where you have agreed beforehand, provides that the Company can disclose it when it is necessary; 1) to outsource the work or 2) for some other justifiable reason.
  5. If you wish to review your personal information, please contact to the relevant contact person we show on the website where you supplied or registered your personal information. The Company will make the efforts to appropriately respond to your request.
  6. The Company will make reasonable efforts to maintain and improve security to ensure that personal information is managed safely.
  7. While complying with applicable laws and regulations, the Company will make ongoing efforts to improve and upgrade measures taken to protect personal information. 
    * With regard to inquiries regarding personal information supplied or registered by you, requests to review such information, etc., should be directed to the contact person indicated at the specific website where the information was submitted.
    * If you are under the age of 13, you are requested to obtain the consent of your parent or guardian, before your personal information is submitted.

## 2\. Cookies

  1. Cookies are small data files that are written to your hard disk when you visit a website. They are used, for example, to identify you when you revisit the website at a later time. The information contained in cookies is exchanged between the website and your Web browser program, but websites are not allowed to read information from cookies created by other websites or other data on your hard disk.
  2. Many websites use cookies, but you may set your Web browsers to inform them before accepting new cookies or to refuse all cookies, if you so wish.
  3. The Company's website occasionally uses cookies to enhance the information and services provided, and to make navigating the site more convenient. The Company's website does not use cookies to obtain information that would allow it to identify you except in cases where you have agreed to provide such information beforehand.

* * *

Local navigation area begins from here.
